digitimes.com 2018-11-13

# Privacy policy

Privacy policy

DIGITIMES gathers personal and non-personal information via its website. Personal information is collected when you subscribe/register on our websites.

DIGITIMES does not release, sell or rent personally identifiable information about our readers to other companies. The information we collect is only used to better understand our readers' interests and fulfill requested services, such as sending out electronic newsletters. Users have control over their personal data via our website. We will retain your information for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the requested services, and such information will be promptly deleted upon the user's request.

Non-personal information is collected through tracking and ad serving technologies by us or by third parties.

We use web traffic monitoring software that records information from visitors' browsers, including IP addresses and pages selected.

Our third party providers may be collecting non-personal information or using cookies in order to display ads and provide us with website traffic reports.

DIGITIMES is currently using the following providers:

We use cookies on the DIGITIMES websites to ensure functionality on the website. None of the DIGITIME cookies include personal/user information and they are not used for tracking.

DIGITIMES uses a third party online payment provider, National Credit Card Center of R.O.C. (NCCC). All of the online credit card transactions are handled by our provider using their payment platform. DIGITIMES does not store your card information on its servers.

Any substantial changes to this privacy policy will be announced prominently on our pages.

If you have any concerns or suggestions about our privacy policy, please contact us.
